http://www.newarkmuseum.org/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
Directions
GET DIRECTION
Privacy Policy
The Newark Museum is committed to protecting the privacy of our online visitors. This privacy policy explains what information we collect and how we use it.
We do not collect personal information about our visitors except when it is knowingly provided. In choosing to provide this information, you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of the Newark Museum’s Privacy Policy.
Anytime you would like to be removed from our database, you may send an email to webmaster@newarkmuseum.org requesting removal.
Occasionally, the Museum may share the information you provide with other organizations whose services might interest you, for instance other area cultural organizations. Your information is never sold or rented to any third party. Further, your email address is never sold, rented or shared with any third party. If at any time you prefer not to have your information shared in this way, you may indicate this by sending an email to webmaster@newarkmuseum.org indicating your intention.
The Museum collects information throughout this website for several different purposes, which are explained below. In certain instances, the Museum uses Third Party vendors to securely process certain transactions or provide a specific service. These services are governed by their own privacy and information security policies. Links to those policies are provided. Beyond providing the services outlined below, your financial information such as credit card information is never shared. In addition, your credit card information is not downloaded to the Museum’s local servers.
Information Collected and Stored Automatically
Anonymous information
The Museum website automatically collects some anonymous information about you when you request pages through your browser such as the IP address or domain from which you access our website, the date and time of your visit and pages you visit. This information is used to help us monitor how you and other visitors use the site, allowing us to provide better service throughout the site. The information collected automatically by the web server does not contain anything that can identify you personally (such as your email address or name) and is stored for the Museum’s use only. The Museum does not sell, rent, or offer this information to third parties.
Cookies
For certain services provided on this website, such as the Museum Shops shopping cart, cookies are sent to your browser and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies are small text files that allow you to save information locally so you will not have to re-enter it the next time you visit. The information we collect from cookies will not be used to create profiles of users and will only be used in aggregate form. You may set your browser to refuse cookies. If you so choose, you may still gain access to most of the Museum website, but you may not be able to conduct certain types of transactions, such as building a shopping cart.
Purchases at the Museum’s Online Shop
The Museum Shop will ask you to provide personally identifiable information necessary to fulfill your online order. When you make a purchase, your credit card information is encrypted and stored on a secure server hosted by UniteU. We will retain your name, address, phone and email address to facilitate customer service, and to inform you of our products and promotional offers.  Please see the UniteU Privacy Policy for more information about how UniteU uses this information. The Newark Museum does not sell, rent, share or give out customer information obtained from our online store.
When you Make a Donation or Purchase a Membership Online
The Museum will ask you to provide personally identifiable information necessary to process and service your Membership or Donation. Your credit card will be stored on a secure server hosted by Blackbaud’s NetSolutions. Credit card information is not visible or downloaded to the Museum’s local servers. We will retain your name, address, phone and email address for our records and to facilitate service to our Members and Donors. Please see the Blackbaud NetSolutions Privacy Policy for more information about how Blackbaud handles this information.
When you Purchase a Ticket Online
The Museum will ask you to provide personally identifiable information necessary to process and service your ticket purchase. Your credit card information will be stored on a secure server hosted by Tix.com or Eventbrite and used only for processing your online transaction. Credit card information is not visible or downloaded to the Museum’s local servers. We will retain the personally identifiable information you provided for our records, and to facilitate customer service. Please see the Tix.com Privacy Policy and Eventbrite Privacy Policy for more information on how this information is handled.
Email Communications
The Museum regularly sends email newsletters and event notices to our registered visitors using a services hosted by MailChimp. Email recipients may opt-out at any time by following the unsubscribe instructions included on all email messages. Please see the Mailchimp Privacy Policy for more information on how Patron Mail handles your email information.
Emailing the Museum
If you email the Museum, your message and email address may be saved by the Museum. Any message, material, business information, ideas, concepts, or other information sent to the Museum by email will be treated as non-confidential and non-proprietary.
Children Under Thirteen Years of Age
The Newark Museum is concerned about protecting children's privacy on our website. We do not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under thirteen years of age. If an identified child sends an email to the museum, we will only use it to respond to the writer and will not retain or use any information concerning the sender.
Links to other Websites
This website contains links to other websites.  These links are provided as a courtesy to our visitors. These links do not imply endorsement of any opinions or ideas expressed therein, or guarantee the validity of the information provided on these sites.
If you have any questions about this privacy policy, the Museum's online practices, or your dealings with this website, you may contact:
Webmaster
Newark Museum
49 Washington Street
Newark, NJ 07102-3176
Email: webmaster@newarkmuseum.org
Telephone: 973.596.6550
Disclaimer
We cannot guarantee the website will be error-free. However, we make every reasonable effort to make sure content is accurate, reliable and complete. This includes correcting any errors that are brought to our attention. You can contact us at webmaster@newarkmuseum.org.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
The Museum may revise this Privacy Policy at any time. We encourage you to periodically visit this page to review our most current policy. Your continued use of this site shall constitute your acceptance of any such changes to the policy.
Closed: New Year's Day, July 4, Thanksgiving Day & December 25.
49 Washington Street,
Newark, NJ
07102-3176 | TERMS OF USE | PRIVACY POLICY
© 2020 THE NEWARK MUSEUM OF ART
Closed: New Year's Day, July 4, Thanksgiving Day & December 25.
@Newark Museum
A few spots still remaining for tomorrow evening's "Paint Night at the Museum - A Winetasting Event" -- Friday, January 31, 5-8 pm #paintnight #winetasting @NewarkMuseum A 21+ event. https://t.co/RKigyMf9l0
Directions
The Newark Museum of Art
973.596.6550
49 Washington Street,
Newark, NJ
07102-3176
GET DIRECTIONS
Adult Group: 973.596.6550
School Group: 973.596.6690
Membership: 973.596.6686
The Newark Museum of Art is committed to making its collection, buildings, programs and services accessible to all audiences.
For more information click here
Contact Us
Name *
Email *
Choose Department *
- Choose Department -DevelopmentDirector's OfficeEvent RentalHuman ResourcesMembershipPublic RelationsSchool Groups
Write your comment... *
Leave this field blank
Hours
Monday - Sunday
10am - 5pm
Thursday-Sunday: 10:00 am–5:00 pm
Monday, Tuesday, and Wednesday: closed; school groups only (except MLK Jr. Day)
To reserve your tour, call 973.596.6690
Closed: New Year's Day, July 4, Thanksgiving Day & December 25.
@Newark Museum
A few spots still remaining for tomorrow evening's "Paint Night at the Museum - A Winetasting Event" -- Friday, January 31, 5-8 pm #paintnight #winetasting @NewarkMuseum A 21+ event. https://t.co/RKigyMf9l0
Directions
The Newark Museum of Art
973.596.6550
49 Washington Street,
The Newark Museum of Art is committed to making its collection, buildings, programs and services accessible to all audiences.
For more information click here
49 Washington Street,
Newark, NJ
07102-3176 | TERMS OF USE | PRIVACY POLICY
©
2020 THE NEWARK MUSEUM OF ART
